<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Mambodyssee]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Mambodyssee]]></description>
        <link>http://mambodyssee.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 08:02:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://mambodyssee.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reading Newspapers, Magazines and Books]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Reading Newspapers, Magazines and Books</h1><p>No matter what the child's age is, he or she will certainly benefit from possessing a broad vocabulary. Not only will an enriched vocabulary help to improve your child's academic performance but it can be a lifelong asset that can be utilized in the business world.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mambodyssee.com/enrich-your-childs-vocabulary-in-4-easy-steps/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3374570e-f097-4ff8-90fd-7c4f38d7697a</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 08:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How do you choose the right bed linen for a baby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How do you choose the right bed linen for a baby</h1><p>There are quite a few things that first time parents tend to not even consider when they are preparing their home for a new family member, and bed linens are perhaps the most egregious example of this behavior.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mambodyssee.com/how-do-you-choose-the-right-bed-linen-for-a-baby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a0052555-4479-4300-b35f-e5ef3b8ad580</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2016 16:17:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What to Eat if You Want to Have an Easy Pregnancy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>What to Eat if You Want to Have an Easy Pregnancy</h1><p>Women who are pregnant often experience unpleasant physical side effects from carrying the extra weight. There are ways to reduce the amount of pressure and stress the body undergoes during this time. The foods a mother to be eats will significantly impact how her body performs during the pregnancy. There are certain foods experts recommend eating when pregnant, which not only benefit the mother, but benefit the baby as well. One item to eliminate from the diet is salt. Pregnant women often retain water, which adds to the pressure in their veins causing their legs and ankles to swell. Getting rid of additional salt will dramatically reduce the amount of swelling associated with pregnancy.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/dd2a9e15-3ef7-4392-9fa0-7a00715cf2ac.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mambodyssee.com/what-to-eat-if-you-want-to-have-an-easy-pregnancy/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4fc1a0dc-df07-499b-9db3-4debf53bb6c0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2016 18:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>